{
    "subject": "David_E._Durston",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "I_Drink_Your_Blood",
    "human_readable": "David E. Durston directed the film I Drink Your Blood.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8891564011573792,
            "question": "What is the title of the film directed by David E. Durston?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8857092261314392,
            "question": "Who directed the film 'I Drink Your Blood'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8024657964706421,
            "question": "Is David E. Durston a filmmaker?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7263780832290649,
            "question": "Are there any other films directed by David E. Durston?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4854974150657654,
            "question": "What genre might the film 'I Drink Your Blood' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4468333423137665,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'I Drink Your Blood'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36929449439048767,
            "question": "What year was 'I Drink Your Blood' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.349643737077713,
            "question": "Were there any sequels or spin-offs made from 'I Drink Your Blood'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2743638753890991,
            "question": "Has 'I Drink Your Blood' received any critical acclaim or awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2323690503835678,
            "question": "What impact did 'I Drink Your Blood' have on the horror genre?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=David E. Durston directed the film I Drink Your Blood.",
            "html": "yago_12579_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'I Drink Your Blood' received any critical acclaim or awards?",
            "html": "yago_12579_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any sequels or spin-offs made from 'I Drink Your Blood'?",
            "html": "yago_12579_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was 'I Drink Your Blood' released?",
            "html": "yago_12579_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_65.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_12579_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide multiple references to David E. Durston being associated with the film \"I Drink Your Blood\", including being its director, and providing specific details about the film's plot, production, and release. Therefore, based on this information, it can be concluded that David E. Durston directed the film I Drink Your Blood."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references to David E. Durston directing the film \"I Drink Your Blood\" in various contexts, thus supporting the triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}